autobarn.net 2012-10-04

# Policies

 **AutoBarn.com Privacy Policy**

**We are committed to maintaining your privacy.**  
To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, AutoBarn.com has developed a Privacy Policy to engender trust and confidence in our site and the Internet by encouraging full disclosure and informed consent. This statement discloses the privacy practices for the AutoBarn.com web site. Questions regarding this statement should be directed to AutoBarn.com through our [Customer Service Center.](http://www.autobarn.net/support.html)  
---  

**Information We Use & How It is Collected**  
**Your IP Address**  
An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer every time you browse the Internet. When users request a page from our site, our servers log the user's current IP address. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our Web site. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous.  
  
**Cookies**  
"Cookies" are pieces of data your browser stores on your computer's hard drive. They enable us to determine when you or someone using the same browser you previously used revisits AutoBarn.com. Cookies also enable us to create a more personalized shopping experience for you. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to refuse them. AutoBarn.com does not use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer. Our policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or any other third parties with links on our site.  
  
**Other Information We Collect**  
When you purchase a product we ask you for information such as name, address, and credit card information. We store and use this information so we can process your order. If necessary, we might use this information to contact you for help processing your order. From time to time we send out notices by email of special offers or sales on our site. If for any reason, you do not want to receive these notifications, just contact us through our [Customer Service Center](http://www.autobarn.net/support.html), or contact us using one of the methods listed below under How to Contact Us. Each email offer also includes simple instructions on how to remove your e-mail address from future mailings.

Whenever you send us personal correspondence, such as e-mail or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the site, we may collect and store such information. From time to time, AutoBarn.com holds contests and sweepstakes. We will collect and store all information relating to such contests and sweepstakes. AutoBarn.com might purchase information from third parties in order to supplement the information we have received from our customers.  
  
**Third-Party Web Beacons**  
 We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here](https://reports.web.analytics.yahoo.com/optout,OptOut.vm?domain=a.analytics.yahoo.com).  
   
**Removing Your Information from Our Records**  
If for some reason, you want us to remove your credit card and contact information from our database, we will, but only after all of your transactions have been completed. All you have to do is send us e-mail at [customerservice@autobarn.com](mailto:CustomerService@autobarn.com), or contact us using one of the methods listed below under How to Contact Us. Such information, however, is never completely removed from our database archives because we routinely back up our servers for disaster recovery and tax-record purposes.  
  
**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**  
**Personal Information**  
Personal information includes your name, e-mail address, mailing address, method of payment information and other data that identifies you as an individual. Your personal information is used by AutoBarn.com, our suppliers and shippers in order to process and ship your orders. AutoBarn.com does not sell, trade, rent or release your personal information to third parties. If we do so in the future, you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" beforehand.  
  
**Aggregate Information**  
AutoBarn.com occasionally shares aggregate data about customers, traffic patterns, sales, and other site information with partners, vendors, and other reputable third parties. This data, however, does not contain any personally identifying information. For example, we don't disclose that you purchased a specific product, but we might share statistics on how many customers have purchased a specific product.  
  
**Legal Issues**  
AutoBarn.com discloses personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on AutoBarn.com or its site; protect and defend the rights or property of AutoBarn.com, the site, or the users of AutoBarn.com; and act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of AutoBarn.com, its site, or the public.  
  
**Other Sites' Policies**  
You might choose to leave our site via links to other sites, including those of advertisers. AutoBarn.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content on those sites, nor is it responsible for the cookies those sites might deposit on your hard drive.  
  
**Safety & Security**  
**Credit Card Security**  
Shopping on the Internet is incredibly safe. 

At AutoBarn.com, we ensure that it's safe by transferring all of your personal information, including your name, address and credit card, over a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) line. This ensures that your information is encrypted and cannot be read by others as it travels over the Internet. The secure mode begins when you initiate your order. You will know you're in secure mode when the tiny padlock icon, located at the bottom of your browser, appears as "locked." You also can verify you are in secure mode by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https." After the information reaches AutoBarn.com, it is stored on a secure server, which means it resides behind a firewall and cannot be accessed from outside the company. At that point, your information can only be accessed by employees to process your orders. All such employees sign a privacy/security policy, which provides legal confidentiality protection for our customers. Violations of this policy results in disciplinary actions, including the possibility of termination, criminal prosecution and civil action.  

**AutoBarn.com's Safe Shopping Guarantee**  
Shopping with us is so safe we guarantee it with our Safe Shopping Guarantee. In a nutshell, we guarantee every transaction as 100 percent safe. If unauthorized charges appear on your credit card as a result of shopping with us while using our secure server, we will reimburse you up to the maximum $50 legal liability. We only require that you follow the reporting steps required by the issuer of your card (under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges).  
  
**Website Errors**  
Prices and availability of products and services are subject to change without notice. Errors will be corrected where discovered, and Auto Barn reserves the right to revoke any stated offer and to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions including after an order has been submitted and whether or not the order has been confirmed and your credit card charged. If your credit card has already been charged for the purchase and your order is cancelled, Auto Barn will issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the charge. Individual bank policies will dictate when this amount is credited to your account. If you are not fully satisfied with your purchase, you may return it in accordance with Auto Barn's Return Policy.  
  
**Your Consent/Contacting Us**  
**Your Consent**  
By using our Web site, you are consenting to the collection, storage, and dissemination of data as described above. We will post any changes to our privacy policy on this page so you can readily review our most current policy. AutoBarn.com also reserves the right to e-mail you regarding changes to our Privacy Policy or any other matters AutoBarn.com thinks is necessary for the administration of the site.  
  
**How to Contact Us**  
We're interested in your comments about our privacy policy. You can send general comments about it to us through our [ Customer Service Center](http://www.autobarn.net/support.html). You also can use that e-mail address to:  
   
**Other Methods of Contacting Us**  
| **E-mail:** |  [Use Our Customer Service Center](http://www.autobarn.net/support.html)  
---|---  
**Phone:** | 1-888-484-9560 or 516-484-9500  
**Fax:** | 516-484-4341  
**U.S. Mail:** | AutoBarn.com  
PO Box 100  
Roslyn, NY 11576  
Attention: Customer Service  
  
_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

 _This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._
